comrademao.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy Policy – Comrade Mao

This privacy policy describes how ComradeMao.com uses and protects any information that you give us. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. There are no personal information that is required to use the service(s) of ComradeMao.com but the meta-data such as ip address, browser name and so on which are used for point system on ComradeMao.com. As a result, everyone using ComradeMao.com can be assured that the information collected by ComradeMao.com will be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, ComradeMao.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. ComradeMao.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how ComradeMao.com’s visitors use its website.

ComradeMao.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. ComradeMao.com does not use IP addresses to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to ComradeMao.com choose to interact with ComradeMao.com in ways that require ComradeMao.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that ComradeMao.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, Internet Protocol (IP) address and username of the visitor is collected to add points to their balance.

In each case, ComradeMao.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with ComradeMao.com. ComradeMao.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. ComradeMao.com will never ask for personal information such as real-name, or credit-card information.

All of the information that is collected on ComradeMao.com will be handled in accordance with GDPR legislation.  
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

ComradeMao.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of project administrators, employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on ComradeMao.com’s behalf or to provide services available through ComradeMao.com, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using ComradeMao.com, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. An example of this case is Google Analytics used to measure the traffic to ComradeMao.com.

ComradeMao.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to project administrators, employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, ComradeMao.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, if you give permission to have your information shared, or when ComradeMao.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of ComradeMao.com, third parties, or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of a ComradeMao.com website and have supplied your email address, WComradeMao.com may rarely send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with ComradeMao.com. We primarily use discord channel to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum.

ComradeMao.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Use of personal information**

We use the information you provide to register for an account, receive newsletters, use certain other services, or participate in the ComradeMao open source project in any other way.

We will not sell or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email.  
Legal grounds for processing personal information

We rely on one or more of the following processing conditions:

our legitimate interests in the effective delivery of information and services to you;  
explicit consent that you have given;  
legal obligations.

**Access to data**

You have the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all your personal information, please follow the instructions at the end of this policy.

ComradeMao.com user accounts can be edited by following these steps:  
1) Visit http://comrademao.com/login/, and then enter your username and password.  
2) Go to http://comrademao.com/edit-profile/.  
3) Edit any information that you feel to add or remove then click on “Update” button at the bottom of the page.

**Retention of personal information**

We will retain your personal information on our systems only for as long as we need to, for the success of the continuing the services of ComradeMao.com.

ComradeMao.com will not delete personal data from logs or records necessary to the operation, development, or archives of the ComradeMao project.

When deletion is requested or otherwise required, we will anonymize the data of data subjects and/or remove their information from publicly accessible sites if the deletion of data would break essential systems or damage the logs or records necessary to the operation, development, or archival records of the ComradeMao project.

**Rights in relation to your information**

You may have certain rights under data protection law in relation to the personal information we hold about you. In particular, you may have a right to:

request a copy of personal information we hold about you;  
ask that we update the personal information we hold about you, or independently correct such personal information that you think is incorrect or incomplete;  
ask that we delete personal information that we hold about you from live systems, or restrict the way in which we use such personal information (for information on deletion from archives, see the “Retention of personal information” section);  
object to our processing of your personal information; and/or  
withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal information (to the extent such processing is based on consent and consent is the only permissible basis for processing).

If you would like to exercise these rights or understand if these rights apply to you, please follow the instructions at the end of this Privacy statement.

**Third Party Links**

Our website may contain links to other websites provided by third parties not under our control. When following a link and providing information to a 3rd-party website, please be aware that we are not responsible for the data provided to that third party. This privacy policy only applies to the websites listed at the beginning of this document, so when you visit other websites, even when you click on a link posted on ComradeMao.com, you should read their own privacy policies.

**Aggregated Statistics**

ComradeMao.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites.  However, ComradeMao.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described in this policy.

**Cookies**

Additionally, information about how you use our website is collected automatically using “cookies”. Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, ComradeMao.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at ComradeMao.com’s sole discretion. ComradeMao.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.  
Contact

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you by contacting tyr@comrademao.com
